singledadsguidetolife.com 2019-06-30

# Privacy Policy | The Single Dad's Guide to Life

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to http://singledadsguidetolife.com and The Single Dad’s Guide to Life and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to The Single Dad’s Guide to Life include http://singledadsguidetolife.com. The The Single Dad’s Guide to Life website is a Lifestyle, Parenting, Film, News and Information. site. By using the The Single Dad’s Guide to Life website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

## Collection of your Personal Information

In order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, The Single Dad’s Guide to Life may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:

– First and Last Name  
– E-mail Address

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through The Single Dad’s Guide to Life’s public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.

## Use of your Personal Information

The Single Dad’s Guide to Life collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.

The Single Dad’s Guide to Life may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from The Single Dad’s Guide to Life and its affiliates.

## Sharing Information with Third Parties

The Single Dad’s Guide to Life does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.

The Single Dad’s Guide to Life may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is transferred to the third party. The Single Dad’s Guide to Life may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to The Single Dad’s Guide to Life, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

The Single Dad’s Guide to Life may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on The Single Dad’s Guide to Life or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of The Single Dad’s Guide to Life; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of The Single Dad’s Guide to Life, or the public.

## Tracking User Behavior

The Single Dad’s Guide to Life may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within The Single Dad’s Guide to Life, in order to determine what The Single Dad’s Guide to Life services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within The Single Dad’s Guide to Life to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

## Automatically Collected Information

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by The Single Dad’s Guide to Life. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the The Single Dad’s Guide to Life website.

## Use of Cookies

The The Single Dad’s Guide to Life website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize The Single Dad’s Guide to Life pages, or register with The Single Dad’s Guide to Life site or services, a cookie helps The Single Dad’s Guide to Life to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same The Single Dad’s Guide to Life website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the The Single Dad’s Guide to Life features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the The Single Dad’s Guide to Life services or websites you visit.

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

## Security of your Personal Information

The Single Dad’s Guide to Life secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. The Single Dad’s Guide to Life uses the following methods for this purpose:

– SSL Protocol

When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.

We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.

## Children Under Thirteen

The Single Dad’s Guide to Life does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

## Opt-Out & Unsubscribe from Third Party Communications

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from third-party partners of The Single Dad’s Guide to Life by contacting us here:  
– Web page: https://singledadsguidetolife.com/  
– Email: toastycritic@gmail.com  
– Phone: 9494660253

## E-mail Communications

From time to time, The Single Dad’s Guide to Life may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication. In order to improve our Services, we may receive a notification when you open an email from The Single Dad’s Guide to Life or click on a link therein.

If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from The Single Dad’s Guide to Life, you may opt out of such communications by Contacting Us or directly unsubscribing..

## Changes to this Statement

The Single Dad’s Guide to Life reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.

## Contact Information

The Single Dad’s Guide to Life welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that The Single Dad’s Guide to Life has not adhered to this Statement, please contact The Single Dad’s Guide to Life at:

The Single Dad’s Guide to Life  
13012 Ramsey Dr.  
La Mirada, California 90638

Email Address:  
toastycritic@gmail.com

Telephone number:  
9494660253

###### Effective as of May 25, 2018
